As dawn shines on us every morn
每当朝阳照耀我们
The fire of friendship is reborn
友谊之火便再重燃
And all the friendships we have made
所有我们之间的友谊
We cherish in every way
我们将竭力珍惜
Loyalty binds us and makes us strong
忠诚凝聚使我们强壮
Honesty shows that we belong
诚实彰显我们心相向
And kindness shared will unite us through each day
善意流露让我们永远团结
The fire of friendship lives in our hearts
友谊之火在心永不熄
As long as it burns, we cannot drift apart
只要它长存  我们永不分离
Though quarrels arise, their numbers are few
争吵虽有  但微不足道
Laughter and singing will see us...
欢笑声和歌唱将伴身...
...through
...旁
Will see us through
将伴身旁
We are a circle of pony friends
让我们把友谊共相守
A circle of friends we'll be to the very end
友谊共相守  直到天长和地久
Though the winter brings all its cold and storm
冬季带来了严寒和风暴
The glow in our hearts keeps us warm
但心中热情在燃烧
The friends we know called our family
我们朋友实则为家人
Will always see us through
永远陪伴我们
Loyalty binds us and makes us strong
忠诚凝聚使我们强壮
Honesty shows that we belong
诚实彰显我们心相向
And kindness shared will unite us through each day
善意流露让我们永远团结
The fire of friendship lives in our hearts
友谊之火在心永不熄
As long as it burns, we cannot drift apart
只要它长存  我们永不分离
Though quarrels arise, their numbers are few
争吵虽有  但微不足道
Laughter and singing will see us...
欢笑声和歌唱将伴身...
...through
...旁
Will see us through
将伴身旁
We are a circle of pony friends
让我们把友谊共相守
A circle of friends we'll be to the very end
友谊共相守  直到天长和地久
翻译
轮回
润色
包子  Loadhe
校对
森林金雨  Loadhe
背景图绘制
Sonicdramon
时间轴
BronyDee  Loadhe
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看